hikarabita kotoba wo tsunai de
connecting old words that have been used up
soredemo bokura shinpuru na omoi wo tsutaetai dake na no
I just want to convey my simple thoughts
fukinukeru kusunda ano hi no kaze wa
that day's faint wind blows away
kinou no haikyo ni uchi sutete
at the castle ruins of yesterday
kimi to warau ima wo ikiru no da
I'll laugh with you and live for the moment
soredemo ano dekigoto ga kimi wo kurushimeru daro
still that incident will continue to trouble you, right?
dakarakoso sayonara nanda
that's why it must be good-bye
konomama nanimo nokorazu ni anata to wakachiau dake
leaving nothing behind, let us share what is left
yagate bokura wa sore ga subetee dato kigatsuite
in time, we'll realize that it was everything
kanashimi wa hoo wo tsutatte namida no kawa ni naru dake
and sadness will touch our cheeks, creating a river of tears
yureru omoi wa tsuyoi uzu ni natte tokeau no yo
Trembling thoughts swept into a vortex and melting away
Who're you guys?
I'm in a bad mood right now.
If you wanna continue to fight,
I won't go easy on you.
You stop your babbling, weakling.
Hey, come over here.
I'm gonna play
do-re-mi-fa-so-la-ti-do on you...
while I snap your ribs!
I'll do it!
What?! He got both of my legs
with his string...!
Why you...!
Humph! Let's hear a nice sound.
Do!
W-What?!
Re!
Wh-Where is he attacking from?!
Your bones make
a really low sound, don't they?
Let's hear a much sharper reverberation,
shall we?
Right?
Next I'll go for
a mi-fa-so tri-combination.
Wha...?!
What?!
Last!
Lions Barrage!
The Sound's
Invitation
Here you are!
I'm digging in!
Sakura-chan! Go on, eat, eat!
The Chinese-style barbecued pork
ramen noodles here are fabulous!
Don't worry. It's my treat.
Right, chef?
You're gonna treat your girl.
You're growing up aren't you, Naruto?
Wh-Wh-What?!
Wh-What the heck are
you talking about?
I need to have an important conversation
with Sakura-chan today...
Sh-She's not my girl
or anything like that...
Sakura-chan?
Sorry, Naruto. I was little spaced out.
This looks delicious.
Now then... Let's eat! Let's eat!
Yeah! Tell me about Sasuke
while we eat.
Sasuke-kun told me not to tell you this
Naruto but...
It's all that guy Orochimaru's fault...
S-Stop!
Kakashi-sensei said it would be fine
and I'd like to believe that too...
But when he was battling Gaara...
Earlier today...
Sasuke-kun was wearing the same expression
as the time before.
That's why I...
Orochimaru, huh?
I ran into him again a little while back.
Really? Where?!
When I was searching for
Granny Tsunade...
Die!
Damn!
Pervy Sage and the old lady...
Despite the fact that
he was fighting two of them at once
he was incredibly powerful.
He's one dangerous dude.
That strong...
It'll all be fine.
Sasuke wouldn't fall to
that kind of guy's enticement.
He's already a really powerful guy
so he wouldn't need to do
that kind of thing!
I guarantee it!
Yeah!
Why does Orochimaru-sama
want this guy anyway?
Kimimaro would have
been much better...
Well, if you stay in
a seedy place like this
you'll just remain mediocre at best.
You'll never become strong...
Wh-Why...?
All my barrages were solid.
Yet this guy...
doesn't seem to have
sustained any damage.
If you keep on fooling around
playing Ninja with your friends
you're just gonna continue to rot.
Come with us.
If you do,
Orochimaru-sama will empower you.
There's no meaning
if we take you by force he said.
You decide.
Gimme a break...
Orochimaru-sama sure sent me
on a bothersome mission.
Hey! What did you decide?
Are you coming?
Or are you not coming?!
Decide already!
When a weakling like you lags
it makes me wanna just finish you!
Try me...!
You... those Curse Marks...
Don't be so sure that
you're the only favorite
of Orochimaru-sama.
One shouldn't use Curse Marks
that lightly.
Or rather... it looks like you're not
even able to control the Curse Marks.
If they continue to be released
for a long period of time
Curse Marks will progressively
eat your body.
It looks like you're still at first state
so the speed at which they will
eat away at you is still fairly slow.
But when they have entirely eaten you
you will lose yourself.
Forever.
In exchange for having been
empowered by Curse Marks
you will be tethered
by Orochimaru-sama.
We no longer have anything
like freedom.
In order to receive something
one must discard something.
What is your objective?
Are you and your comrades
just going to comfort each other
in this lukewarm village...
then simply forget all about...
Uchiha Itachi?
Don't forget your objective.
This kind of village does
nothing more than shackle you!
Cut your stupid ties with this place.
If you do that you'll...
be able to obtain much
more fabulous power.
Don't forget your objective!
Thanks!
H-Hey, Sakura-chan.
I'll walk you home!
Huh? Don't worry about it.
Why, why?
The streets are dangerous at night!
They're well lit so I'll be fine...
Sakura-chan?
Thanks Naruto.
But I want to go home alone tonight.
I see...
I'll be fine!
Yeah!
Why are you hanging around in a place
like this in the middle of the night?
One has to pass down this road
to leave the village.
Go home and sleep.
Why...
Why won't you tell me anything?
Why are you always silent like that?
You won't tell me one single thing.
Why should I have to tell you anything?!
I'm telling you to keep your nose
out of my business.
Stop bothering me
over everything I do.
I... make you dislike me
all the time, don't I?
Do you remember?
We just became Genin and
the Three-Man Teams were assigned...
You and I were alone for
the first time here at this very spot.
You got mad at me.
See! That guy doesn't
have parents, right?
He's all alone and he doesn't have to deal
with parents lecturing him...
That's why he can sometimes
be selfish!
Solitude...
Huh?
Isn't it the same as being
scolded by one's parents.
What's the matter all of a sudden...
You... are annoying...
I don't remember that.
Yeah, I guess...
that was long ago after all...
But it all began that day.
Sasuke-kun and me...
And also Naruto and Kakashi-sensei...
The four of us went
on various missions, didn't we?
Those were tough and
difficult times but...
But...
more than anything...
it was so much fun!
I know about your family, Sasuke-kun...
But revenge...
that won't bring anyone happiness.
No one...
Neither you...
nor I.
As I expected...
I'm different from you guys...
I'm walking a road that's incompatible
with the rest of you.
The four of us worked together...
and it's true that there was a time
when I thought that was my road.
The four of us have worked together
but in the end
I decided on revenge.
That's been my reason for living.
I can't become like
you and Naruto.
Are you going to isolate
yourself again, Sasuke-kun?!
You taught me that solitude
is a very rough thing that time, Sasuke-kun!
Now I know exactly how that feels.
I have both family and friends...
But if you were no longer here, Sasuke-kun...
for me...
for me it would be the same as solitude.
From here again...
we're going to start walking
our new paths individually.
I...!
I love you so very very much, Sasuke-kun!
If you would only be with me, Sasuke-kun,
I won't let you regret it
no matter what!
I'll make it fun every day and
you will definitely find happiness!
I'll do anything for you, Sasuke-kun!
So... I'm begging you,
please stay here!
I'll even help you with your revenge!
I'll make it happen somehow
I promise you...!
So stay here... with me...!
If that doesn't work for you...
Then take me with you...
You really are... annoying.
Don't go!
If you go I'll scream and...
Sakura...
Thank you...
Sasuke-kun...
We were waiting for you, Sasuke-sama.
What's your intention?
It was already decided that
you would be our leader
the moment you exited the village.
Please forgive our rudeness
up to now.
I don't care about any of that.
Let's go.
This is the beginning!
GET UP aa sumimasen
get up! oh, I'm sorry
goku tama ni boku tama ni
once in a long while, once in a while
yume ni yabureru hito no kakera ga
the remnants of a person broken by dreams
yama no you ni mieru
kamisama ni hotokesama ni
clinging to God, clinging to Buddha
sugari naiteru hito no kakera ga
the remnants of a person crying
yama no you ni mieru
danran dansu de RANDEBUU
rendezvous with a happy dance circle
ore shouri no poozu da randaran
this is my victory pose, round and around
SHEIKU SHEIKU SHEIKU sagasou janai
shake shake shake let's look
owaranai baibai no RIZUMU de
with a bye-bye rhythm that never ends
yama no you ni mieru
What? That jerk Sasuke.
What the hell is he thinking?
He has such a twisted personality!
What is it that he disliked so much
that he'd do something like this?!
Damn! I'm not about to let that guy
do whatever he wants!
If things come to this I'll chase him
down to the end of the world.
I'll drag that guy back
even if I have to grab him by his neck!
Next time:
"Gather! The Iron-Wall Formation."